myfatpocket.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy

To My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd, your privacy is of utmost importance. Hence, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd wishes to let you know what information My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd collect when you visit the Website, how My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd collect such information, and how My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd use such information. By accessing the Website, you consent to the data practices described below. Please note that My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may periodically make changes to the privacy. As such, please remember that it is your responsibility to remain informed about any changes.

  * (a) Information My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may collect from you and how does My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd collect such information

My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may periodically request at times that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. For example upon registration at the Website, personal information which may include any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number(s) and other contact information may be required from you. My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may also request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information as well as public information such as user ratings and reviews and other information you view on the Site.

Some of the information collected by My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may not be explicitly submitted by you as My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd also automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, the web pages you request, your browser type and language, access times, and the referring web site address. For example, when you visit the Website, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our Site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may also automatically collect information about your online activity on the Website, which may include, but not limited to, the Sellers you have visited, the products you have browsed or purchased, and the searches you have conducted on the Site. Generally, most browsers will automatically accept cookies, but you may choose to modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on the Website. The information My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd obtain in this manner enables My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd to customize the services offered by i) the Website and ii) the Sellers on the Website, so as to better cater to your needs and to measure the overall effectiveness of our Sellers, content and other activities.

  * (b) How My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may use your information

In general, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may use information from you for the following purposes:

  * • perform research and analysis about your use of the Website, types of products you may be interested in or your shopping patterns. Such research and analysis may be disclosed to the Sellers or to any third parties which in My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd’s sole discretion may deem fit for the purpose of upgrading the Sellers’ services, contents or products which may be offered from time to time;
  * • manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * • communicate with you by e-mail about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * • develop and display content tailored to your interests on the Website;
  * • verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with any contests and giveaways that the Website may have;
  * • enforce the Terms and Conditions;
  * • give away product samples to Buyers who are willing to have their personal information shared with the Sellers from time to time;
  * • manage our business; and
  * • perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

Generally, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd will not share your personal information with others except for purposes relating to the function of the Website, or when My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared.

However, from time to time information such as your full name, profile photo and any personally identifiable information you have included in your profile or ratings may be shown to other users primarily in conjunction with product reviews and ratings you have contributed. In such a case, your personal information may be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. As My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd strongly encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Please note that by accepting this Terms and Conditions, you consent that My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd will not be liable for any loss or damages which may arise from such situations.

My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may also disclose your personal information in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement agency or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may disclose your personal information when My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce the Terms and Conditions.

My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may disclose your personal information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. The personal information which you provide to us is an asset of My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd and may be included in the assets transferred in the event of a substantial corporate transaction.

From time to time, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Terms and Agreements. If the policy relating to the collected information changes at some time in the future, My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd will post the policy changes on the Website to notify you of these changes. My Fat Pocket Pte Ltd will only use the data collected from the time of the policy change for any new purpose. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you may wish to contact My Fat Pocket Data Protection Officer at  [dataprotection@myfatpocket.com](mailto:dataprotection@myfatpocket.com).

  * Withdrawal of Consent

In the event that you wish to withdraw your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal data in our possession or under our control, you shall submit your request to My Fat Pocket Data Protection Officer at  [dataprotection@myfatpocket.com](mailto:dataprotection@myfatpocket.com). We will process your request from such a request for withdrawal of consent being made, and will thereafter not collect, use and/or disclose your personal data in the manner stated in your request. As a result of your withdrawal of consent we will/may not be able to continue to provide you with our services and/or maintaining your existing relationship with us.
